So the next command is sea route.
So sea route helps us to change the directory to the top of the tree.
So for example, so at the moment I'm in a speed l folder I, I'm navigating to build the folder.
Let's get into blueprint folder.
So now I'm within the blueprint folder.
So if I need to come back to the route folder so you can simply type C route, then check you are in
the road folder.
So C route simply helps you to change the directory to the top of the tree.
So next we have the M commands.
So M commands are basically to build aosp.
So we have different variants of RM commands.
So simply giving M will make from top of the tree.
So we'll be using this to build the complete aosp so you can simply go ahead and type m hyphen.
This parameter is optional, but you can specify the number of logical codes to be used while building
aosp so you can pass hyphen J and the number of course you want to use for the build.
And this will just simply start the build.
So I'm just cancelling it.
So RM will make from the top of the tree.
So let's look at hm mm mm hm.
Mm.
Triple and m a and triple m a.
So the M command basically builds and installs all the modules in the current directory and their dependencies.
So as an example, so I am now in the apps folder.
So inside apps folder, I'm getting into one of the app, for example, launcher three.
So from here if I use MM command, it is going to build the launcher three module alone so it will compile
all the dependencies of launcher three.
So now it's going to only compile launcher three, not the complete build.
So please note that a mum command will not install the APK into the image files, so it will only build
or compile the current module.
So this is useful when you make a modification to your project and you want to make sure there is no
compilation issue or anything, but in case if you want to install it into the image, then you have
to use the use either the ADB command to install the APK from the intermediate directory or you could
run the hm command.
So the hm command will change the images.
So m command will not change the images.
And then we have the triple m command.
So in case of triple m, you need to parse the module names.
So let me come back now am in apps folder and from here I'm running and I'm passing launcher two and
maybe calendar app.
So I'm passing, I'm passing two modules into triple m command, sorry launcher three.
So now it will compel two modules, the launcher three and the calendar module.
And again here please note that it won't change the image.
So this is helpful when you want to compile a set of modules which you have changed and to make sure
that nothing is breaking the build.
So I have compiled the modules recently.
That's why it has nothing to do here.
So now we have M let's come back here.
So the M command, it compiles the entire thing and it will build the images.
M compiles only the current directory, so please note it won't install the APK on its own.
If you want to install the pick it to the current emulator, then you need to do it using the ADB command.
Or you can rerun the M command to build the images for you and then we have triple M.
This will build and install all the modules in the supplied directory, send their dependencies and
then we have m a and a, it's same as M and triple.